Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Subject Files, 1963-present UPG.RG.52
ULS Greensburg
- Student Plays [Student One Act Plays; University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Workshop], 2000-2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  2000, Nov. 30-Dec. 1. Sure Thing by David Ives; An Actor's Nightmare by Christopher Durang. Brought to you by affiliates and students of UPG.
  2001, Nov. 28-30. Student One Acts [Student Directed One Acts]. See: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Videocassettes. VC.VII.24a-c. 3 Videocassettes.
  2002, Apr. 4-5. UPG Student Directed One-Act Plays: Moby Dick 2002; Hello Out There; Ghost Story; Mary MacGregor.
  2002, Nov. 21-22. An Eclectic Evening of Radical One Acts: Paul Wolanski's Original Script and World Premier of The Cat Came Back; The Dumb Waiter by Harold Pinter; From Harry Shearer's Le Show, The Taliban Pizza; The Still Alarm by George S. Kaufman
  2003, Apr. 2-3. Student One Acts Presented by the Students of THR0070 Theatre Workshop: The American Way by Lavonne Mueller; Sure Thing by David Ives; Dog Eat Dog by Tim Kelly.
  2004 Mar. 17-18. Performing Arts Society presents: A Journey Through Broadway.
  2004 Apr. 14-15. UPG Presents Student-Produced One-Act Plays: Jumping by William Borden; Dalmation by Conrad Bishop; Lost by Mary Louise Wilson; Locker Room by Tracy Sarpolis; Sally Throws Shot Put by Jack Colavincenzo; Interview by Matthew Calhoun; Koala Talk by Jack Colavincenzo; Interview by Matthew Calhoun; Checkers by Dale Doerman; Property of the Dallas Cowboys by Sam Smiley.
  2004, Dec. 2-3. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Workshop Presents: Student One Act Plays: Donations, PT 1; Transitions by Logan McGarrity; Donations PT 2 by Mike Hardill; Absolution by William Reynolds; Donations PT 3 by Logan McGarrity and David Meglorino; To the Airport by Julianne Bernstein; Donations PT 4 by Mike Greco; Ledge by William Borden; Donations PT 5 by Jackie Schaefers, Jeff Schussler; The Society by J. Omar Hansen; Donations PT 6 by Jack Gibson; A scene from Pulp Fiction by Quentin Taratino; I Wanna Be a Cowboy by John Tuttle; Donations PT 7 by Jackie Schaeffers. [Donations skits were written and acted by Theatre Workshop Students and were a result of in-class improvisations. All plays were directed by Theatre Workshop Students. Transitions was written by Logan McGarrity, a Theatre Workshop Student.]
  [2005, Apr. 7-8. The UPG One Acts: The Newlywed Game by John Gallo and Missy Wess; "Ups" and Downs by Jackie Schaefers and Logan McGarrity; Gossip Girl by Lacy Betters and Casy Schall; Every Cloud Has a Silver Lining by Lacy Betters and Josh Troy; 50's Sexual Education Video by Michael Hardill and Traci Pullman; Verizon Guy VS. Lil' John by Dave McMeekin; Jehovah Comes Knocking by Meg Thompson and Andy Mischick; Cereal Love by Michael Hardill; Tarot Card Reading by Rebecca Brunner and Matt Schimizzi; Dr. Phil and John Madden Hour by Mark Hardill; Airplane Safety by Jackie Schaefers; Lacy Betters: Anti-Christ by Casey Schall and Lacy Betters; I Didn't Audition to be a Stripper by Andy Mischick and Meg Thompson; Medical Malpractice by Lacy Betters and Casey Schall; Comedian by Zach Kocian; Albino Midgets in Bikinis by Tony Karanikas and Michael Hardill. Written solely by the Theatre Workshop class.
  2005, Dec. 1-2. The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theater Workshop Class is proud to present One Acts, written, directed and performed by the students of UPG's Theater Workshop Class: Love Kept in the Closet by Jamie Pope; Shutter Speed by Elaine Galinskie; Lucky Ticket, by Lauryn Carnes; Day Dream by Daniel Waajid: Find Your Lover by Adam Zeleznick; Thanks a Latte by Rebecca Depretis; Plumbing for Ghosts by Alisha Dick; The Impact by Kathryn Clymer; Lost by Josh Troy and Anthony Karanikas; What a Good Girl is Thinking by Kelly Mallon; Mobile School by Daniel Waajid; Wonder by Josh Troy and Anthony Karanikas.
  2006, April 11, 12. The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Workshop class is proud to present One Act Plays partially written, completely directed, and performed by the Students of UPG's Theatre Workshop Class. Plays and Characters: Priceless; The DMW One by Nick Zagone; DS 1 by Daniel Waajid and Steve Sargent; Downtown by Jeffrey Hatcher; A Guy Walks in to a Bar by Rob Hack; DS 2 by Daniel Waajid and Steve Sargent; Queenie by David Kaye; Zero Wireless; Dumb Blond Anchors by Daniel Waajid; Super Duper Computer Store; DS 3 by Daniel Waajid and Steve Sargent; Punk'd by Chad Smith, Justin Innocent and William Johnson; Excerpt from Clerks by Kevin Smith; Eye to Eye by Christopher Graybill; DS 4 by Danile Waajid and Steven Sargent; Mint Juleps by Nick Zagone; Sure Thing by David Ives; Greensburg Idol by Becky Depretis.
  [200?] The Ugly Duckling by A.A. Milne performed by Student Players of UPG. Directed by Jeremy Tennent.
- Student Writing Awards [UPG Student Writing Awards], 1994-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Sponsored by the English Writing department at UPG.
  1994 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize ["Named for Gerald Stern, Pittsburgh born poet who has authored a number of volumes of poetry and who won the 59th Fellowship of the Academy of American Poets for distinguished poetic achievement, the Stern Prize provides for a $100 cash award." See: UPG News Release 5/6/88. For additional information on Stern, See: UPG News Release, 5/7/97. 1st awarded in 1994.] Jackie Dillon
  1995 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize Mark Romah Carrie Jo Fox, 1st Honorable Mention Adam MacGregor, 2nd Honorable Mention Jennifer F. Boch, 3rd Honorable Mention
  1996 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize [Awardee unidentified]
  1997 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize Jennifer Currie Andrew Cooper, Honorable Mention Brett Warman, Honorable Mention
  1998 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize Angela Ciotti Matt Falo, Second Place Melissa Barkley, Honorable Mention
  1999 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize [Awardee unidentified]
  2000 Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize, Romy Shinn Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. David Brobec
  2001 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Karen Scott Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Gregory J. Harold Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Brian Root
  2002 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Gregory Harold Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Janet Stanley Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize.Michael Allshouse
  2003 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Joseph Reed Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Donna Weaver Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Jared Bajkowski
  2004 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Danielle Danna Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Mark Steinman Ida B. Wells Prize for Creative Non-Fiction. Julie Stefanko Ida B. Wells Prize for News Feature Reportage. Adam Matcho
  2005 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Dawn Sherwood Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Edwin Kunkle Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Laura Poko Ida B. Wells Prize for Journalism. Adam Matcho
  2006 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Timothy Gebadlo Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Brandon Cleary Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Christopher Carrolli Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Adam Matcho Literature Award. Alexandra Gray
  2007 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Timothy Gebadlo; Heather Gustine Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Jason Downey Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Dylan Nice
  2008 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Kelly Scarff Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Dylan Nice Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Lorenzo Lista Ida B. Wells. David Streett Junior English Literature Prize. Michelle Sarver Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Jamie Mathews, Michelle Sarver
  2009 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Alyssa Sauter Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Michael Zindren Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Joel Gazal Ida B. Wells. Ashley Macik Junior English Literature Prize. Matthew Reilly Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Kalley Burtnett; Deidre Stuffer
  2010 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Elizabeth Russell Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Matthew Reilly Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Joy Pinkney Ida B. Wells. Kirstin Kennedy Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Deidre Stuffer; Corey Florindi Literature Award. [No award listed in Honors Convocation Program for 2010. faz]
  2011 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Kimberly Wolff Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Megan Hughes Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Janelle Sheetz Ida B. Wells. Rachel Kuskie Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Joseph Saccamago Jr., Corey Florindi Literature Award. Alexander Miskalls
  2012 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Khalil Zeigler. Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Elliot Sheedy. Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Kayla Strutt. Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Runner-up: Shannon Sankey Ida B.Wells Journalism Prize. Kaylie Harper. Ida B.Wells Journalism Prize. Runner-Up: Manda Morrison Pitt-Greensburg's Award for Excellence in Digital Media Writing [Awarded 1st time in 2012]. Michelle Boring. Honorable mention: Justin McKeel. Junior Literature Essay Prize. Katie Pagano Award for Excellence in Digital Media Writing. Michelle Boring.
  2013 Composition Research Award [Annual Pitt-Greensburg Composition 2 Research Award]. Steven Reddy. Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Megha Pai. Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Andrew Brown. Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Colin Gabauer. Junior Literature Essay Prize. Kelly Stewart. Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Megan Hughes; Kelly Stewart Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Maggie Donohue. Award for Excellence in Digital Media Writing. Michelle Boring.
  2014 Composition Research Award. Adam Slater. Gerald Stern Poetry Award. Keegan Love. Ida B. Wells Journalism Award. Colin Gabauer. Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Kyle Holland. Junior Literature Essay Prize. Luke McDermott. Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Michelle Dempsey. Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Emilie Hrabak.
  2015 Composition Research Award. Nicole Johnson. Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Shannon Sankey. Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Michelle Boring. Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Kelsey Campbell, Michelle Dempsey, Elizabeth Gerda, Alexa Martin. Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Kyle Holland.
  2016 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Brooke Lawrence. Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Calley Tinley. Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award. Matti Tyskewicz. Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Gretchen Uhrinek. Composition Research Award. n.b.: Not awarded in 2016.
  2017 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Jason Rivenburg Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Shelby Newhouse Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Gretchen Uhrinek Composition Research Award. Fiona R. Carter
  2018 Gerald Stern Poetry Prize. Kara Goughnour. Scott Turow Fiction Prize. Shelby Newhouse. Ida B. Wells Journalism Prize. Alexandra Dimoff. Joan Didion Creative Nonfiction Prize. Alyssa Fry. Essay in Literature Prize. Alyssa Fry.
  2019 Joan Didion Award for Excellence in Creative Nonfiction Winner: Kaylee Hauck, "Carnelian" Honorable Mention: Emily Buckel, "Loneliness"
  Scott Turow Prize for Excellence in Fiction Winner: Kaylee Stinebiser, "Modern Indecency" Honorable Mention: Brianna Dettlinger, "Ocean Eyes"
  Gerald Stern Prize for Excellence in Poetry Winner: Matt Boyer, "Six Poems" Honorable Mention: Kriza Bruno, "Excerpts from Dominicana Americana"
  Ida B. Wells Prize for Excellence in Journalism Winner: Madison Jarnot, "Pitt Faculty Files for Union Election" Honorable Mention: Chelle Jackson, "Pitt-Greensburg Searches for New President"
  See also: Creative Non-Fiction Week and Literary Festival [Creative and Professional Writing Prizes]
- Summer Science and Mathematics Experience (SSME), 2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Includes: CD of Powerpoint Slide Presentation at the 2010 Residency Program.
- Teacher Education Programs (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- Tree of Life Synagogue Congregation Tragedy, October 27, 2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Contains: Message from Chancellor Gallagher to the University of Pittsburgh community on the occasion of the shooting of 11 members of the Tree of Life synagogue in the temple on Saturday morning, 27 Oct. 2018; Listing of "Pitt Cares: Community Resources" [University, Local Events, Regional Events, National/Continental]. Action News 4, Show Transcript, 4/28/2019: "Squirrel Hill Stands Against Violence" [community organization].
- United Way of Westmoreland County (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- UPG Ambassadors [UPG Presidential Ambassadors], 2006-2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Presidential Ambassadors Induction Ceremony. 2006-2014, 2016-2018
  See also: UPG.RG.60. Ser.: Prints. UPG Ambassadors.
  See also: UPG.RG.60. Ser.: Flash Drive (FD2) UPG Ambassadors Induction Ceremony 2011
- UPG Arts Ambassadors, 2002-2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  History: UPG Arts Ambassadors formed in 2002 as "… a group of alumni and friends interested in promoting the development of the arts at UPG and making them available to the people of the region.." Mission: "To support the arts programs at the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg by promoting the quality and diversity of offerings to the community and to encourage the financial underwriting to sustain and maintain the program.
  File, 2002-2004. Contains: Poster: "The UPG Arts Ambassadors: A Partnership for Excellence"; invitational list to an arts fund-raising dinner, June 26, 2002; List: the Arts Ambassadors programs which includes a report on the 2002 activities; issues of the UPG Arts Newsletter, Jan.,-Feb. 2002, Spring 2004, Ruben Alfonso Lopez Nieto, University of Gurnajuato, Mexico."
- UPG Chorale [UPG Collegiate Chorale; Pitt-Greensburg Chorale; UPG Chorale & Chamber Singers], 2001, 2009 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Organized Fall, 2001.
  Chamber Singers debuted in the Spring 2009 Concert.
  For DVD of concert, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD37
- UPG Community Cookbook, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  [published by the UPG Staff Association, Spring, 2000] 88 p. [contains recipes from members of the UPG community and sold at $10 per copy to raise money to support the Frank A. Tosatto Scholarship Fund]
- UPG Concert Band [Bobcat Concert Band; UPG Band] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- UPG Distinguished Teaching, Professional Development, and Service Awards, 1992-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  Initiated in 1992 by the UPG Administration. Awards given for Distinguished Teaching, Professional Development, and Service. First awards given in 1993.
  Year Teaching Development Service
  1993 Mark McColloch Judith Zimmerman Mary Grace O'Donnell
  1994 Richard Blevins Diane Marsh Ruth Kuschmierz
  1995 Lillian Beeson Alicia Covarrubias Mary Beth Spore
  1996 Anthony Boldurian Rakesh Bhatnagar No Award
  1997 Joanne Viano No Award Kerry Holzworth
  1998 Sayre Greenfield Frank McGlynn Patricia Duck
  1999 Donald Reilly No Award Colette Levin
  2000 Walter Orange Stephen Murabito Lillian Beeson
  2001 Larry J. Whatule Nancy Florez-Estrada Guy M. Nicoletti
  2002 Timothy Savisky Mary Beth Spore Tom Wolf
  2003 Martha Koehler No Award Barbara Barnhart
  2004 Randi Koeske Sayre Greenfield No Award
  2005 Diane Cheek No Award Kerry Holzworth
  2006 Shujiang Lu Jeffrey Sposato Christine McCreary
  2007 No Award No Award Mark Stauffer
  2008 Kelli Maloy Ryad Ghanam Randi Koeske
  2009 Elisa Beshero-Bondar Edward Krisner Lou Ann Sears
  2010 Matt Luderer William Pamerleau Nancy Estrada
  2011 Paul S. Adams Richard L. Blevins Amber McAllister
  2012 William Pamerleau Kelli Maloy Donald Gibson
  2013 Kristen Asplin Gary Hart Benjamin Espinoza
  2014 Melissa Marks Jessica Everly Frank Wilson
  2015 Vickie Barnot Gary Lutz John Prellwitz
  2016 Barbara Barnhart Mark Stauffer Anne Czerwinski
  2017 Amber McAlister Elisa Beshero-Bodnar Pilar Herr
  2018 Anne Czerwinski Jonathan Vallano William Rued
  2019 Russell Phillips III Stacey Triplette Timothy Holler
- UPG Emerging Leaders Development Series [UPG ELDS] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
  See also: UPG.RG.60 Prints. UPG Emerging Leaders Development Series-Graduation
- UPG Families Association (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 1)
- UPG Leadership Conference [Student Leadership Conference], 2001-2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  UPG Archives: [3rd] 2001, Mar. 17; 6th, 2004, Oct. 23; 11th, 2009, Nov. 7; [20th] 2018, Nov. 3
- UPG Management Sciences Lecture Series (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2)
- UPG Performance Collective, 1999-2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2, Map-case 1)
  The UPG Performance Collective is a student performance group at UPG. Their first performance as the UPG Performance Collective was The Visit by Friedrich Durrematt, Mar. 23-26, 2000. The group's first production was The Memorandum by Vaclav Havel, Nov. 12-14, 1999, and presented under the name of the UPG Players. Dr. Kimberley May Jew is the director of the UPG Performance Collective.
  See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--UPG Peformance Collective. For posters: See: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: UPG Performance Collective. [filed in Map Case]
- UPG Performance Collective Productions, 1999-2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  *See UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Video Cassettes. VII 23.1-10.
  1999, Nov. 12-14. The Memorandum by Vaclav Havel. *2000, Mar. 25-26. The Visit by Friedrich Durrematt. *2000, Nov. 10-12. Beyond Therapy by Christopher Durang. *2001, Mar. 15-18. The Adding Machine by Elmer Rice. 2001, Apr. 4, 5, 7. Sorry Wrong Number by Lucille Fletcher; Zoo Story by Edward Albee *2001, Sept. 13-15. UPG Performance Collective Presents The UPG Regional One-Act Festival: *The Little Red Gate By Maureen Jenkins, Directed by Sue Danks; *Not Lightly Chosen by Robert C.Wittig, Directed by Christopher Scott. *2001, Nov. 7-10. The Lion in Winter by James Goldman. *2002, Mar. 21-23 Suburbia by Eric Bogosian. [UPG lacks program] *2002, Nov. 6-9 Such Foolish Affected Ladies by Moliere *2003, Mar. 21-22 Taking With by Jane Martin *2003, Nov. 20-22 R.U.R. (Rossum's Universal Robots) *2004, April 1-3 Fool for Love by Sam Shepard
- UPG Players (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  [Variant Names: Pitt-Greensburg Drama Club; Pitt-Greensburg Little Theater; Pitt at Greensburg Little Theater; Little Pitt-Greensburg Theater]
  See: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Players for oversize materials.
  See also: UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--UPG Players UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Video Cassettes--VII. Performing Arts--UPG Players
- UPG Players Productions, 1967-2001 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 2)
  As [Pitt-Greensburg Little Theater]:
  1967, Dec. 1-2. The Sandbox by Edward Albee; Hello Out There by William Saroyan.
  1968, Mar. 6-8. Harvey by Mary Chase.
  1968, Dec. Hocus-Pocus by Jack Poppelwell.
  1969, Aug. 31-Sept. 2. The Acting Lessonby William Simms; Mrs. Dolly has a Lover by William Hanley.
  [1969, Nov. 19-22]. The Lady's not for Burning by Christopher Fry.
  1969, Mar. 13-15. Antigone by Jean Anouilh.
  As Pitt-Greensburg Drama Club:
  1979, April 6-8 Inherit the Wind by Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee
  1979, Oct. 7 The Proposal by Anton Chekov
  1980, Mar. 28-30. The Tragedy of Ragweed Cowboy Joe by I. E. Clark
  1981, Apr. 10, 11, 12 The Threepenny Opera by Bertold Brecht.
  1982, Jan. 30 Ferry Boat: The Zoo Story by Edward Albee.
  1984, Mar. 22, 23 Spoon River Anthology by Edgar Lee Masters.
  1985, Mar. 22, 23 University by Jon Jorry
  1986, Mar. 21, 22 24 Hours-AM Plus [15 mini-play written by various artists]
  1987, Apr. 3-4. The Mouse that Roared by Ryan T. Shaffer.
  1988, Apr. 14, 15, 16 Dark of the Moon by Howard Richardson and William Berney.
  1989, Apr. 6, 7, 8 A Thurber Carnival and Other Fables by James Thurber.
  1990, Apr. 5, 6, 7 Animal Farm by George Orwell; Listen to the People by Stephen Vincent Benet.
  1991, Apr. 4, 5, 6 The Insect Play by Karel Capek
  As UPG Players:
  1997, Nov. 20, 21. Two One Act Comedies by Anton Chekhov: The Proposal and The Bear.
  2000, Mar. 30, 31. Overruled by George Bernard Shaw; Doubles by Georges Feydeau.
  2001, Mar. 22, 23. Fit to be Tried by Georges Feydeau; 'Dentity Crisis by Chrisopher Durang.
  * This list of Productions may be incomplete; this list includes only those which have been indentified. [faz 3/27/01].
  See Also: UPG.RG.57 Faculty Papers. McWhinney, Dr. Norman C. Ser.: Theater Activity. [faz 2/6/2018]
- UPG President's Scholarship Fund (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
- UPG Safety Committee (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
- UPG Sports Pep Band (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
- UPG Staff Association (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
- UPG Staff Recognition Program [Annual Holiday Luncheon and Staff Recognition Program] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3)
  For photographs See Also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Staff Awards Luncheon Visual Images--Negatives
- UPG Theater Dept. Productions, 2004-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 7, Box 3, Map-case 1)
  [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Company; Pitt-Theatre Company; Pitt Greenburg Theatre Company]
  2004 Nov. 18-20. Picasso at the Lapin Agile by Steve Martin. [First production directed by Tavia La Follette.] See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Poster. [housed in Map Case]
  2005 Apr. 14-16. Faust: A Masked Telling. Tavia La Follette, director, artist, mask designer; David Kwiatkoski [Dave Kaye], scenic designer and technical director; Dan Fisher, stage manager and sound designer; Sheila Confer, lighting director.
  2005, Nov. 17-19. The Compleat Works of Shakespeare (Abridged) written by Adam Long, Daniel Singer and Jess Winfield. Directed by Stephen A. Schrum.
  2006, Mar. 23-25. Medea by Euripides. Translation by Ian Johnston, Malaspina University-College, Nanaimo, BC, Canada. Choral ode texts by Steven Schrum. Original music composed by Jade Shames except choral odes music by Amie Millward. For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 1 Medea
  2006/07 Season
  2006, Sept. 28. The UPG Theatre Company presents a staged reading of "H-Bomb: Fission, Fusion, Fission", the drams of the Teller-Ulam dispute, by Helene Smith and Charles Haldane.
  2006, Oct. 5. Immaculate Miscocveptions. A monologue performance by Stephen A. Schrum. Special Musical Guest Jeremy dePrisco. [For first performance, June 16, 18, 2006, See: RG52 Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous).] For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 2 Immaculate Misconceptions.
  2007, Jan. 25. Pitt-Greensburg's Red-Eye Project
  2007, Feb. 2-4. Greensburg American Opera Co. The Telephone by Gian Carlo Menotti; The Impressario by W. A. Mozart. For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 4 The Telephone & The Imperessario.
  2007, Mar. 29-31. Mother Courage and Her Children by Bertolt Brecht. featuring original music composed for the show by Pitt @ Greensburg students Ashley Peer, Chad Smith and Eric Durant. For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 5A, B Mother Courage and Her Children
  2007/08 Season
  2007, November 15-17. House of Blue Leaves by John Guare. Music and Lyrics by John Guare. Directed by Stephen A. Schrum. For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD 9A, B. The House of Blue Leaves.
  2008, April 3-5. The Miser by Moliere. For DVD, See; UPG.RG.60 DVD 10A, B. The Miser. See also: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Greensburg American Opera.
  2008/09 Season
  2008, November 20-22, Four one-act plays: Hard Candy by Jonathan Rand; Lifeline by Douglas Craven; 4:48 Psychosis by Sarah Kane; Actor's Nightmare by Christopher Durang. For DVD, see UPG.RG.60 DVD 11A, B. "An Evening of One Acts".
  2009, April 2, 3, 4. Wonder of the World by David Lindsay-Abaire. For DVD, see UPG.RG.60 DVD 12A, B. Wonder of the World
  2009/2010 Season
  2009, November 19-21. The Duchess of Malfi by John Webster. For DVD, See: UPG.RG.60 DVD13, The Duchess of Malfi